sw-box.com 2010-04-11

# Privacy Policy - Safe, Secure Online Shopping - From Professional Wholesale Distributor

www.sw-box.com knows that you care how information about you is being used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This following notice details our privacy policy. By accessing this site, you are accepting the practices described in this Notice. Both mentions of "Cellphonezone Limited; " and/or "www.sw-box.com" effectively refers to this site where you are accessing now.

 **What Personal Information About Customers does sw-box.com  maintain?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at www.sw-box.com . It is NOT used for commercial benefits or re-selling purposes. Here are the types of information we gather.

**Information Provided By You:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You may choose not to provide certain information, but then you would not be able to take advantage of many of our features. Information that you provided for such purposes is used to effectively responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies", and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.sw-box.com . Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

**E-mail Communications:**  
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from www.sw-box.com  if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this by selecting " un-subscribed" in the newsletters menu.

**Information from Other Sources:**  
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

**What About Cookies?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as automatic login and permanent shopping carts for storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.  
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of  www.sw-box.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**Does sw-box.com Share the Information It Receives?**  
Information about our customers is an integral part of our business, and we are not interested in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries controlled by www.sw-box.com and as described below.

**Agents:**  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**Promotional Offers:**  
Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of www.sw-box.com customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your account newsletter preferences as that is how we will send out our promotions.

**Business Transfers:**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that www.sw-box.com, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

**Protection of www.sw-box.com Dealers and Others:**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; legal enforcement or apply our [Terms & Conditions ](http://www.sw-box.com/terms-and-conditions.html)and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of www.sw-box.com, our own users, or others. This includes exchanging information with appropriate companies and diligent organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**With Your Consent:**  
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**Security**  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using diligent and trusted payment processors. Credit card processing is done at the server end of the payment processors, without exposure to either www.sw-box.com, subsidiaries, or business affiliates. Payment processors are critically selected, and they protect your privacy and information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption algorithm that creates a secure data channel in which your information is transferred.  
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**What Information Can I Access?**  
www.sw-box.com provides you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.

**What Choices Do I Have?**  
As detailed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such www.sw-box.com features as Automatic login, and permanent shopping carts. You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "My Account" pages. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. Speed is a luxury and it is essentially a barrier if crucial information to enable efficiency of your transactions is affected. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this in the newsletter menu.

**Terms & Conditions, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit www.sw-box.com , your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms & Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of Malaysia and China. If you have any concern about privacy at www.sw-box.com, please send us a thorough description to support@sw-box.com, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms & Conditions will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

**Automatic Information**  
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click-stream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for.
